yourlocalblog.com 2011-12-31

# Your Local Blog

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is critically important to us. At YourLocalBlog, we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  

  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy that incorporates these goals: 

It is YourLocalBlog’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, YourLocalBlog collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. YourLocalBlog’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how YourLocalBlog’s visitors use its website. From time to time, YourLocalBlog may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

YourLocalBlog also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. YourLocalBlog does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to YourLocalBlog’s websites choose to interact with YourLocalBlog in ways that require YourLocalBlog to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that YourLocalBlog gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with YourLocalBlog are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, YourLocalBlog or the transaction processor, collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with YourLocalBlog. YourLocalBlog does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
YourLocalBlog may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, YourLocalBlog may monitor the most popular blogs on the YourLocalBlog.com site. YourLocalBlog may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, YourLocalBlog does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
YourLocalBlog discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on YourLocalBlog’s behalf or to provide services available at YourLocalBlog’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using YourLocalBlog’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. YourLocalBlog will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, YourLocalBlog discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when YourLocalBlog believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of YourLocalBlog, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a YourLocalBlog website and have supplied your email address, YourLocalBlog may occasionally send you an email to tell you about system enhancements, upgrade opportunities, new features, to solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with YourLocalBlog and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. YourLocalBlog takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. YourLocalBlog uses cookies to help YourLocalBlog identify and track visitors, their usage of YourLocalBlog website, and their website access preferences. YourLocalBlog visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using YourLocalBlog’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of YourLocalBlog’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by YourLocalBlog and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, YourLocalBlog may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in YourLocalBlog’s sole discretion. YourLocalBlog encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
